(Sheldon:)Correction.
Missy can date whoever she wants.
- Look, we have to settle this.
- I agree.
(Leonard:)Sheldon's sister is hiding at Penny's
because we've all been hitting on her.
She's not hiding. She needed to call her
grandmother, who's apparently very sick.
(Raj:)Oh, and then I believe
she has to wash her hair.
(Howard:)Oh, you poor deluded bastard.
- Don't start with me, dude.
- You wanna go again?
(Missy:)- Sit down.
- Okay.
If we're gonna fight over Missy,
let's do it the right way.
The honorable way.
HOWARD:
Ow! Ow, ow, ow.
LEONARD:
Take that.
You want some more?
(Leonard:)And he's down.
MAN [ON TV]:
One, two, three, four...
- Come on, come on! Get up.
- Stay down, bitch.
Seven, eight, nine, 10.
[BELL DINGS ON TV]
Yeah! Natural selection at work.
(Sheldon:)I weep for humanity.